kingsouq.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy

It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. 

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When you browse our website, we may collect your IP address, browser, operating system, and the URL you request. 

When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your IP address, the date and time, name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or other information, your PayPal email and your PayPal shipping address, the details collected from the customers do not include credit card details. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. The personal details collected will not be shared or sold to any third parties. All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties. 

We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use ‘cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

To quickly process your transactions.

o administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 

They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link. 

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

Refund Policy

The refund would happen through the original mode of payment only. 

Cancellation Policy

As long as the shipment has not left our warehouse,the order may be cancelled.Cancellations can be carried out by mailing us at service@kingsouq.com 

If the shipment has already left our warehouse, we won’t be able to cancel the order. In case of receipt of damaged or defective items through courier, please report the same immediately to our Customer Service team. This should be reported on the same day of receipt of the parcel. 

Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). 

Changes to our policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on Dec 1th, 2014. 

Questions and feedback

we welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

*Recommended statement is “Any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with this website shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of UAE.

*The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the Customers’ are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.

Contact Us

Need Assistance Before Purchase: sales@kingsouq.com

Need Assistance With Order: service@kingsouq.com

Need Assistance After Delivery: support@kingsouq.com

Tel: +971 4 2564 551 (10 lines)

Phone Work Timing, Sunday-Thursday AM 11:00-PM 2:30 PM 5:30-PM 11:30 UTC/GMT +4

Add:Shop 1-2, Opp Ferrari Hotel, Behind Musalla Road,Deira,Dubai UAE P.O.Box:52376 Dubai UAE
